bmwmotorcycles.com 2008-06-16

# BMW Motorcycles: : Privacy

## Privacy Policy

### Our Promise to You

We appreciate the trust you place in BMW Motorrad USA and would not want to jeopardize your trust in any way. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. Rest assured that we will not rent or sell your personal information to anyone. 

BMW works with retailers and contracted business partners to provide you with products and services and to give you the best ownership experience possible. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect your personal information. We will address your privacy-related questions or concerns. 

### Our Commitment to Privacy

#### What information does BMW Motorrad USA collect?

As part of providing you with our products and services, we obtain "personal information" about you, such as your name, address, email and phone number.

#### How does BMW Motorrad USA use my information?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to facilitate efficient transactions and provide you with information regarding relevant products and services. BMW will not do anything to jeopardize your trust, including renting or selling your personal information.

#### What information does BMW Motorrad USA share?

We share personal information with members of the BMW Group, to assist us in providing offers for products or services that may be of interest to you. Members of the BMW Group include, BMW North America, BMW Financial Services, BMW Bank of North America, and BMW Insurance Agency. We share personal information with non-affiliated companies that provide services on our behalf. All of these companies are contractually obligated to keep the personal information that we provide to them confidential and to use such information only to provide the services we ask them to perform. We also share personal information with non-affiliated companies that market our products and services, such as our retail centers who are distinct entities and have their own privacy policies. 

#### Is my information secure?

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect personal information. We also employ encryption technologies and user authentication procedures that are designed to keep your data secure. We limit access to personal information to authorized personnel and contractors who need access to perform their job and are contractually required to keep your information secure. 

#### How am I updated on BMW Motorrad USA's privacy policy?

As business conditions change, we will update this policy to reflect changes in our business practices. We will post revisions to our policy on our web site. 

#### Questions and Comments

Please feel free to send your privacy-related comments or questions to [privacy@bmwmotorcycles.com](mailto:privacy@bmwmotorcycles.com) or write: BMW Motorrad USA, Customer Relations and Services PO Box 1227, Westwood NJ 07675-1227. You may also call Customer Relations at 800-831-1117 Prompt "Customer Service Motorcycle".

Thank you for your continued interest in BMW Motorrad USA.
